

Tiago Rato Web Developer



# ABOUT ME

I'm a determined, diligent person who discovered the love for programming. Having worked abroad for 10 years, I adapt very easily to multicultural environments.

I'm eager to learn, and I like to improve myself to become a better and valuable member of a team.



# CONTACTS



+351 966 695 370



★ tiagorato13@hotmail.com



Vialonga, Portugal



https://www.linkedin.com/in/tiagorato



https://github.com/TiagoRato13



## 🗎 SKILLS AND ABILITIES

HTML / CSS Node.js

JavaScript

MongoDB

React SQL



## INTERESTS









Movies



**Board Games** 





# EDUCATION

#### FullStack Web Developer course (Ironhack, Lisbon, Portugal)



January 2023 – March 2023

Bootcamp program, over 500 hours focused on MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS) JavaScript, HTML and CSS.

Create 3 full stack projects on each of the 3 modules presented using REST API's and CRUD operations:

- Monster at the end of the tunnel
- Precoce
- Maria Psicóloga

### FullStack Web Developer course (Codemaster, Portugal)



n December 2021 – July 2022

Learn basic to advanced level with multiple tasks to complete as well as a real final project including HTML/ CSS, PHP, SQL, Bootstrap and JavaScript (minimal), having finished with a final score of 19 out of 20.

## Divemaster/Instructor Program (Roctopus, Koh Tao, Thailand)



anuary 2018 – May 2018

### Bachelor of Cookery and food production

(Estoril Higher Institute for Tourism and Hotel Studies, Estoril, Portugal)



September 2007 - June 2010

# **EXPERIENCE**

## Contractor (Habinterior, Lisbon, Portugal)



September 2020 - Present

Operate and implement coordinated work programmes for smooth-running site operations. Maintain work in line with budget and schedule.

## Dive Instructor (Roctopus Dive, Koh Tao, Thailand)



may 2018 - August 2020

Listen to client's concerns, provide additional information to ease anxieties and cultivate a relaxed atmosphere to enhance group enjoyment. Instil individuals and groups with confidence and motivation for productive sessions.

#### Chef (London, England)



final January 2011 – June 2017

Supervise all kitchen food preparation, in demanding, high-volume environment and deputise as head chef as needed to maintain team productivity and quality. Recruit and train kitchen staff to meet high expectations for performance and quality.